Elections Research Center Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- State File, 1918-1992 (Box 12-312)
  - North Dakota (Box 212)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1976, (4 folders) (Box 215)
  - Ohio (Box 215)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 215)
      - 1956-1958, (4 folders) (Box 215)
      - 1960-1968, (9 folders) (Box 216)
      - 1970-1976, (10 folders) (Box 217)
      - 1976-1982, (11 folders) (Box 218)
      - 1984-1990, (9 folders) (Box 219)
      - 1992, (2 folders) (Box 220)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 220)
      - 1939-1963, (17 folders) (Box 220)
      - 1965-1978, (17 folders) (Box 221)
      - 1979-1985, (4 folders) (Box 222)
    - Miscellany, 1924-1984, (13 folders) (Box 222)
  - Oklahoma (Box 223)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 223)
      - 1956-1966, (12 folders) (Box 223)
      - 1966-1972, (10 folders) (Box 224)
      - 1974-1980, (13 folders) (Box 225)
      - 1982-1990, (12 folders) (Box 226)
      - 1992, (2 folders) (Box 227)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1956 (Box 227)
    - Miscellany, 1928-1982, (7 folders) (Box 227)
  - Oregon (Box 228)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 228)
      - 1920-1962, (10 folders) (Box 228)
      - 1962-1966, (9 folders) (Box 229)
      - 1968-1972, (7 folders) (Box 230)
      - 1972-1976, (7 folders) (Box 231)
      - 1978-1984, (10 folders) (Box 232)
      - 1986-1992, (8 folders) (Box 233)
    - Miscellany (Box 233)
      - 1932-1969, (2 folders) (Box 233)
      - 1946-1975, (2 folders) (Box 234)
  - Pennsylvania (Box 234)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 234)
      - 1956-1960, (7 folders) (Box 234)
      - 1961-1966, (8 folders) (Box 235)
      - 1968-1974, (10 folders) (Box 236)
      - 1976-1980, (9 folders) (Box 237)
      - 1980-1984, (8 folders) (Box 238)
      - 1984-1990, (9 folders) (Box 239)
      - 1991-1992, (5 folders) (Box 240)
    - Miscellany (Box 240)
      - 1920-1983, (4 folders) (Box 240)
      - 1940-1983, (3 folders) (Box 241)
    - Philadelphia (Box 241)
      - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 241)
        - 1955-1983, (15 folders) (Box 241)
        - 1987 (Box 242)
      - Miscellany (Box 242)
        - 1950-1983, (7 folders) (Box 242)
        - 1982-1986, undated, (3 folders) (Box 243)
    - Pittsburgh (Box 243)
      - 1954-1969, (6 folders) (Box 243)
      - 1973-1977, (2 folders) (Box 244)
  - Rhode Island (Box 244)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 244)
      - 1956-1964, (11 folders) (Box 244)
      - 1964-1972, (11 folders) (Box 245)
      - 1974-1980, (10 folders) (Box 246)
      - 1982-1988, (10 folders) (Box 247)
      - 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 248)
    - Miscellany (Box 248)
      - 1933-1961, 1970-1973, undated, (5 folders) (Box 248)
      - 1974-1986, (4 folders) (Box 249)
  - South Carolina (Box 250)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 250)
      - 1956-1965, (12 folders) (Box 250)
      - 1966-1972, (11 folders) (Box 251)
      - 1974-1984, (18 folders) (Box 252)
      - 1986-1992, (9 folders) (Box 253)
    - Miscellany (Box 253)
      - 1932-1979, (4 folders) (Box 253)
      - 1974-1985, (3 folders) (Box 254)
  - South Dakota (Box 255)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 255)
      - 1956-1966, (12 folders) (Box 255)
      - 1968-1976, (11 folders) (Box 256)
      - 1976-1986, (13 folders) (Box 257)
      - 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box 258)
    - Miscellany, 1920-1978, undated, (5 folders) (Box 258)
  - Tennessee (Box 259)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 259)
      - 1956-1962, (10 folders) (Box 259)
      - 1964-1970, (10 folders) (Box 260)
      - 1972-1976, (9 folders) (Box 261)
      - 1978-1984, (10 folders) (Box 262)
      - 1986-1992, (10 folders) (Box 263)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1959-1975, (6 folders) (Box 263)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1983, (6 folders) (Box 264)
  - Texas (Box 264)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 264)
      - 1948-1956, (7 folders) (Box 264)
      - 1957-1962, (11 folders) (Box 265)
      - 1962-1968, (8 folders) (Box 266)
      - 1970-1974, (10 folders) (Box 267)
      - 1976-1980, (11 folders) (Box 268)
      - 1980-1984, (12 folders) (Box 269)
      - 1984-1990, (12 folders) (Box 270)
      - 1990-1992, (7 folders) (Box 271)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections, 1963 (Box 271)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 271)
      - 1969-1975, (5 folders) (Box 271)
      - 1977 (Box 272)
    - Miscellany (Box 272)
      - 1932-1989, (9 folders) (Box 272)
      - 1966-1975, undated, (4 folders) (Box 273)
  - Utah (Box 273)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 273)
      - 1956-1958, (4 folders) (Box 273)
      - 1960-1972, (14 folders) (Box 274)
      - 1974-1986, (14 folders) (Box 275)
      - 1988-1992, (4 folders) (Box 276)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1959-1975, (5 folders) (Box 276)
    - Miscellany, 1920-1980, (4 folders) (Box 276)
  - Vermont (Box 276)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 276)
      - 1956-1960, (6 folders) (Box 276)
      - 1962-1972, (15 folders) (Box 277)
      - 1974-1984, (15 folders) (Box 278)
      - 1986-1992, (9 folders) (Box 279)
      - 1992 (Box 280)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1987, (4 folders) (Box 280)
  - Virginia (Box 280)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 280)
      - 1956-1964, (10 folders) (Box 280)
      - 1966-1972, (9 folders) (Box 281)
      - 1974-1978, (8 folders) (Box 282)
      - 1980-1988, (12 folders) (Box 283)
      - 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box 284)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections (Box 284)
      - 1955-1961, (9 folders) (Box 284)
      - 1963-1973, (8 folders) (Box 285)
      - 1977-1985, (5 folders) (Box 286)
      - 1989, (2 folders) (Box 287)
    - Miscellany (Box 287)
      - 1924-1979, (5 folders) (Box 287)
      - 1955-1989, (6 folders) (Box 288)
  - Washington (Box 288)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 288)
      - 1956-1957, (3 folders) (Box 288)
      - 1958-1966, (10 folders) (Box 289)
      - 1968-1972, (7 folders) (Box 290)
      - 1974-1978, (7 folders) (Box 291)
      - 1980-1988, (11 folders) (Box 292)
      - 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 293)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1954-1973, (4 folders) (Box 293)
    - Miscellany (Box 293)
      - 1920-1973, (4 folders) (Box 293)
      - 1952-1981, undated, (5 folders) (Box 294)
  - Washington, D.C. (Box 294)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 294)
      - 1956-1960, (2 folders) (Box 294)
      - 1964-1974, (13 folders) (Box 295)
      - 1976-1992, (22 folders) (Box 296)
    - Home Rule referendum, 1974 (Box 297)
    - Miscellany, 1940-1986, undated, (4 folders) (Box 297)
  - West Virginia (Box 297)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 297)
      - 1940-1954 (Box 297)
      - 1956-1962, (10 folders) (Box 298)
      - 1964-1970, (8 folders) (Box 299)
      - 1972-1978, (9 folders) (Box 300)
      - 1978-1984, (10 folders) (Box 301)
      - 1984-1992, (9 folders) (Box 302)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1956 (Box 302)
    - Miscellany (Box 302)
      - 1932-1948, 1956 (Box 302)
      - 1955-1973, 1982, (3 folders) (Box 303)
  - Wisconsin (Box 303)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 303)
      - 1956-1958, (8 folders) (Box 303)
      - 1960-1964, (9 folders) (Box 304)
      - 1964-1970, (10 folders) (Box 305)
      - 1972-1976, (6 folders) (Box 306)
      - 1976-1982, (10 folders) (Box 307)
      - 1984-1992, (12 folders) (Box 308)
    - Mayoral and municipal, 1940-1984, (3 folders) (Box 308)
    - Miscellany (Box 309)
      - 1932-1987, (5 folders) (Box 309)
      - 1980-1982, undated (Box 310)
  - Wyoming (Box 310)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 310)
      - 1956-1968, (13 folders) (Box 310)
      - 1968-1982, (15 folders) (Box 311)
      - 1982-1992, (10 folders) (Box 312)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1965, 1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 312)
- Oversize, 1959-1987 (Box OV 1)
  Printed material.
  Arranged and described according to the series, container, and folder from which the items were removed.
  - State File (Box OV 1)
    - Hawaii (Box OV 1)
      - General elections and primaries
        - Primary election official returns, 1959 (Container 73)
    - New Hampshire (Box OV 1)
      - Miscellany
        - First Primary, 1987 (Container 185)
    - New Mexico (Box OV 1)
      - General elections and primaries
        - Official returns, 1980-1984 (Containers 194 and 195)